Maxime Faget Papers
University of Houston-Clear Lake Archives & Special Collections
- Series XXV: Periodicals
  - Monographs in Aerospace History #4 Enchanted Rendezvous 2 Copies, December 1995 (Box 50)
  - Monographs in Aerospace History #5 Hugh L. Dryden's Career in Aviation and Space, 1996 (Box 50)
  - Air & Space Smithsonian Volume 12 Number 2, June/July 1997 (Box 50)
  - Monographs in aerospace History #9 U. S. Human Spaceflight A Record of Achievement, 1961-1998, July 1998 (Box 50)
  - National Maritime Historical Society Sea History The Art, Literature, Adventure, Lore & Learning of the Sea Number 88, Spring 1999 (Box 50)
- Series XXVI: Oversize
  - NASA Public Information with Oversized Picture, undated (Box 51)
  - Brown Scrapbook, 1965 (Box 52)
  - Presidential Luncheon Honoring Space Shuttle Columbia Astronauts Young and Crippen Scrapbook, 1981 (Box 52)
  - Red Scrapbook (poor condition), undated (Box 53)
  - Yearbooks, 1943-1946 (Box 54)
  - Reel to reel film, undated (Box 55)
  - Reel to reel film, undated (Box 56)
  - Blueprints for the Industrial Space Facility, 1980s (Box 57)
  - Glass Slides Blue of Skylab, undated (Box 58)
  - Unboxed Silver of Shuttle Concepts, undated (Box 59)
  - Antarctica Slides Box 1 - 4, 1967 (Box 60)
  - Antarctica Slides Box 5 - 8, 1967 (Box 61)
  - Antarctica Slides Box 9 - 12, 1967 (Box 62)